No!
不要
No, stop!
不要 快停止
Please, you've done enough!
你已經做夠了吧
No, Kenta!
不要 健太
Don't do it!
不要這麼做
Please, don't come inside me!
請你快點拿出來吧
Stop!
不要
No, Kenta!
健太
I felt this summer was going to be special.
我感覺到今年夏天會很特別
I was kind of excited.
我有點兒激動
I thought of the good things that could come true.
我一直盼望的事可能會成真
Yes, this is Kotomi speaking.
我是琴未 請說
Jinpachi!
陣八
That's fine!
好的
It's time for me to wake up.
我也醒來了
Pool?
嗯 游泳池
But...
但是…
I don't think I can.
真實不好意思啊
Yeah.
是的
Kenta's coming?
什麼 健太
I think I can make it today.
我想我還是去吧
I'd feel bad turning down an invitation.
我覺得拒絕你的邀請不大好
Yes, I'll meet you in front of the pool at 11.
那11點在游泳池前見吧
I haven't seen them since the last day of school.
自上次學校後就一直沒見了 真想他們啊
Maybe I should wear the pink one.
我還是穿粉紅色比較可愛吧
Isaku Respect
遺作 ～Respect～
Episode1: Prison of Shame
第一幕 恥辱的監獄
Kotomi Asakawa
Part A 淺川 琴未
Hey, Kotomi.
琴未啊
What do you see in Kenta?
裡見到健太嗎
Well...
嗯
You like him, right?
你喜歡他 是吧
I think you would be better off with someone older and more mature.
我想你最好還是再成熟些
It's better if...
這樣更好 如果…
the guy knows what he's doing, you know.
他在想什麼你知道嗎
I don't think...
我不知道…
I'm really ready for that yet.
我還真的為那作好準備了
Someone else will get to him first!
可能其他人比例快哦
Competition?
競爭者
It's obvious that Miyuki also likes Kenta...
顯然美由紀 也喜歡健太…
by the way she looks at him.
她看上去很可愛哦
Hi Kotomi!
琴未
Hi, Miyuki!
美由紀
How are you?
你好啊
Fine.
嗯
You didn't expect to see me here?
你很想看這我嗎
It's not that.
不是的
I just talked to Kenta.
我剛剛和健太聊天
You came with him.
你和他一起來吧
We came with friends.
我們和朋友一起來
Akemi was here too, but she left.
明美也一起她剛剛走開了
I wasn't asking for details.
我不想知道這麼詳細
I wasn't implying anything.
我沒暗示任何事情
It's really none of my business.
他真的和我沒關係
Liar!
你撒謊
I have competition.
我有競爭者
What am I doing this for?
我為什麼會這樣
Kotomi.
琴未
Miyuki?
美由紀嗎
Don't look up my skirt!
不要看我裙底
If you're that desperate...
如果你那麼想看…
you can take a good look.
你就好好看吧
Ha!
哼
All men should just...
所有的男兒都應該
disappear.
消失
What!
什麼
Don't!
不要
You should be a lot more careful.
你應該更小心點
It's not like my skirt's short on purpose!
這不是我故意的
I know the wealthy Princess wants a lot of attention...
我知道富有的公主也許想得到更多的注意…
but it's causing problems.
但這樣做會引起其他問題
Don't call...
請不要叫我…
me Princess, because I'm not.
公主 因為我不是
Really, if you're not a wealthy princess...
真的 如果你不是一位富有的公主…
then why do you show off your silk underwear?
那你為什麼在炫耀你的絲綢內衣呢
Is she mean to me...
他在針對我嗎
because she likes Kenta, too?
是因為她也喜歡健太嗎
If that's true...
如果那是真的…
then I can't lose!
我絕對不能輸給她
Why am I thinking about this? It's not worth it.
我不應該想太多了
It's not like I get to make the decision, any way.
無論如何我也要贏
Did mom leave me a note?
這是給我的信
Unbelievable!
不是開玩笑吧
I should have just ignored that goddamned letter.
我根本不應該理那封信
What did your letter say?
你說什麼信
Was yours blackmail?
你也收到嗎
Well, same here.
果然是一樣
Where did they get the info?
到底是誰寫的信
The note was filled with cheap threats.
信中全是威嚇內容
We don't know that for sure, do we?
我不知道是誰做的
The author's skilled at getting blackmail information.
但寫不想是勒索的
I know it's just a prank.
我知道這只是個玩笑
They're having fun watching us freak out in here.
他們一定正在看這我們
I don't think that's the objective.
我認為不是那麼簡單
What do you mean?
你是什麼意思
We all have to focus on protecting ourselves right now.
我們必須從現在起保護自己
That's stupid!
不是開玩笑吧
Then why would they send Kenta a note as well?
那麼他們為什麼假裝健太些信給我們
Maybe he's a target, too.
或許他也是目標之一
Miyuki, where is Kenta, anyway?
美由紀 健太到底哪裡
He went out to look for Ms. Kumi...
他去找久美老師和理香了
Also, a way out of here.
此外 還要找方法離開這裡
I think it's a little too late, but...
我認為已經太遲了
It stinks in here!
這裡很臭啊
I guess I don't have a choice.
我想也沒其他選擇了
Nobody's looking, I hope.
希望沒人看到吧
I'm really sorry to barge in on you like this.
真不好意思在這時候打擾你
Akemi's disappeared, too.
明美已經也不見了
What?
什麼
You, Kenta, and I are the only people left.
只剩下你和健太還有我了
Don't wander off by yourself anymore.
你不要再自己亂走了
Miyuki?
美由紀
What do you think happened to everybody that disappeared?
你知道他們為什麼會突然不見了
You just might find out for yourself...
你自己會有答案的…
if you keep wandering off like this.
如果你再亂走的話
I didn't.
我沒
Kenta was totally freaking out that you were gone.
你亂走健太會很擔心的
He was worried that you disappeared like the other girls.
他擔心你像其它女孩一樣不見了
I need you to promise me...
你能答應我一件事嗎…
that you won't tell Kenta about...
你不要告訴健太 我…
I refuse to lie for anybody.
我不喜歡別人說謊
It's just something you don't want a person you like to know.
這只是不想讓自己喜歡的人知道自己喜歡他
I don't stoop so low as to like men.
我是不會這麼做的 因為我喜歡他
Period.
絕對
So, you don't like Kenta?
因此 你不喜歡健太嗎
Don't worry about me.
你不要擔心我
Don't you know he likes you?
難道你不知道他喜歡你嗎
I also have to ask you to do me a favor.
我還想你能幫我一個忙
I can't believe you had the guts to use this dirty toilet!
我真不能相信你有勇氣用這麼髒的洗手間
Miyuki...
美由紀…
I'm keeping the door open.
我會把門打開
That would be a lot better for me than smelling anybody's piss.
那總比聞著別人的尿味好
That's rude.
這樣不好吧
Tell me, is the princess implying that her urine smells like perfume?
你是告訴我公主的尿象香水一樣嗎
You were holding it for a while.
你這麼長時間
Is that supposed to make it smell even better?
是為了使它更好聞嗎
Will you please stop calling me Princess?
請你不要再叫我做公主了
It's not like I wear silk underwear every day, either!
我不是每天都穿絲綢內衣的
You don't have a sense of humor either.
你一點幽默感都沒有
Why does she enjoy making fun of me?
她為什麼喜愛嘲笑我
What?
什麼
What's wrong?
怎麼了
It's okay!
沒事
It's okay, I got spooked.
不好意思 嚇到你
But...
但是…
I swear, I'm fine.
真的沒事 我很好
If you say so.
你這樣說
What was that about?
那是為什麼
No!
不要
See?
看
Here!
這裡
Ha!
哼
Perv!
窺視
Fine, you can pick me.
好 你能按我
You can watch. The next episode, that is.
你可以繼續觀看下一個節目
This place is just disgusting.
這地方真討厭
I guess I was being too mean.
我想我太卑鄙了
I'd rather...
我真想…
not have to do this.
不這樣做
Maybe I should tell Kotomi about it, too.
或許我也該告訴琴未
No, stop it!
不要 不要這樣
No!
不要
A video was found...
錄像被發現了…
of the girls that disappeared, being raped.
其他人不見後被強姦了
The psycho must be after her, too.
她也需要有最壞的心理準備
No, stop!
不 不要
No!
不要
Should I tell her?
怎麼辦呢
What?
什麼
It's okay!
沒事
It's okay, I got spooked.
不好意思 沒事了
But...
但是…
I swear, I'm fine.
真的 沒事了
If you say so.
你這樣說
I'm getting all worked up.
我要繼續堅持下去
I'm sorry.
對不起
Please excuse me.
真不要意思
Let's just...
讓我們…
forget about this, okay?
忘記這個 好嗎
We're both old and mature enough...
我們成熟些…
to handle this like adults, right?
象成年人一樣處理這個 好嗎
I will, I'll tell her, move the knife!
我會 我會告訴她 請把刀…
Keep pissing.
繼續小便
What?
什麼
He wants to watch you pee.
他想要看你小便
No, stop!
不 不要
I'll say it like you want!
我會照你想的說
I want to watch...
我想要看…
you pee.
你小便
Come on...
來吧…
keep peeing!
一直小便
Please!
求求你
For the two of us, this was only the start...
對於我們兩個這只是開始…
of a horrific night.
一個可怕的夜晚
Episode 2 "Miyuki Sakaki"
Part B 「榊 美由紀」
Hi big sister!
喂 姐姐
She's really cute.
她真可愛啊
That's her only asset.
那是她的唯一資產
Really.
是嗎
You have to check.
你必須檢查哦
You don't want the world to see your panties.
你不想要大家看見你的內褲吧
Thanks.
笨蛋
What are you doing in here?
你在這裡做什麼
So, what was that sigh all about?
為什麼全都是歎氣呢
Anything to do with this cute guy?
都是為了這個人嗎
Give me that!
給回我
Now!
馬上
No!
不給
Don't be a pain!
不給我就…
Right?
是嗎
Are you going to listen to me?
你要聽我的
Nope!
不要
Never!
算了
Fine!
真是的
Ha!
哈哈
Stop it!
等等
No, don't!
不要
So even you get excited when you think about him.
每當想起他你就是興奮吧
Just, cut it out!
快停下來
I don't think you have anything to worry about, at all.
我不認為你有什麼好擔心的
You're really pretty, too!
你這麼漂亮
Wait!
等等
You're still so frigid!
你仍然如此寒冷
This isn't funny, Aimi!
不要這樣開玩笑
You have to be more honest...
你要更坦白哦…
if you want him to notice you.
如果你想他注意你
You can't get past your inhibitions.
你不能穿得這麼保守哦
You can be so immature.
像是還沒發育是的
Shut up!
笨蛋
Fine!
真實的
My sister...
我的妹妹…
was brutally raped and murdered...
被殘忍強姦並且殺害…
about a year ago...
大約一年前…
inside this very building.
在這座大樓裡面
I'm not twisted like you are!
我不喜歡你這樣勒這我
No, stop!
不要
No!
不
Please, I'll say what you want!
我會照你想的說的
No, stop!
胸部
Please, hurry up!
求求你 盡快
I can't do it!
我做不到
I can't, if people are watching!
有人正看 我做不到
No, stop it!
不 不要
Stop, don't hurt me!
不要 走開啊
You psycho!
你個變態
Don't look!
不要看啊
Don't look.
不要看
No!
不要
He's such a sick, twisted bastard!
怎麼辦 發生這種事
That was just so gross!
這樣的事
I have to tell this to everybody!
我必須把這告訴大家
No!
不要
Especially to Kenta, right?
特別是健太 對嗎
No, please don't tell him!
不行 請不要告訴他
So, you lied to me!
果然 你對我說謊了
You like Kenta too, right!
你確實也喜歡健太
Did I tell you that Miyuki, like...
喂喂 美由紀…
farted in front of me?
在我面前小便呢
I like him!
我喜歡他
Yes, I like him!
是的 我喜歡他
So please don't tell him about any of this!
所以請不要告訴他這事
Promise me, Kotomi!
答應我 琴未
Don't tell anybody about this, okay?
不把這告訴任何人 好嗎
Especially not to Kenta!
特別是 健太
Miyuki...
美由紀…
so you did.
果然
I like him, too.
我也喜歡他
No!
不要
Stop it!
住手
I'm begging you!
我求求你
Please don't!
不要這樣做
Stop!
不要
Please, don't make me!
求求你不要
Somebody, help me, please help!
誰來救救我 求求你
I can't do that for you, I just can't!
隊裡我不能這麼做
No!
不要
Please don't make me!
不要這樣 求求你
I just can't!
不可以…
I just can't do it!
不可以這樣做
Kotomi!
琴未
No, don't!
不行
Stop, I just can't!
不要 求求你
He has to be completely crazy!
他是個瘋子
You can't...
不可以…
say anything about this, right?
你不可以告訴任何人
Let's promise each other.
我們答應彼此了
What's going to happen to us?
什麼會要發生在我們身上
Help!
救命
Kenta!
健太
Help us!
救救我們